Oinus, Ainous, Anous, Odious.
Gentlemen Broncos is a comedy, science fiction,
drama film directed by Jared Hess.
A teenager attends a fantasy writers' convention where he discovers
his idea has been stolen by an established novelist.
Benjamin, played by Michael Angarano.
Bronco / Brutus, played by Sam Rockwell.
Ronald Chevalier, played by Jemaine Clement.
Judith, played by Jennifer Coolidge.
Tabatha, played by Halley Feiffer.
Dusty, played by Mike White.
Gentlemen Broncos is a 2009 American comedy film written by
Jared and Jerusha Hess and directed by Jared Hess.
The film stars Michael Angarano, Jemaine Clement,
Jennifer Coolidge, and Sam Rockwell.
The film is about a teenage author whose fantasy story
is plagiarized by an established author.
The film explores themes of writing, plagiarism,
homeschooling, aftercreditsstinger, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.